billhartzer.com 2018-08-15

# Privacy Policy - Bill Hartzer - Search, Marketing, Tech, and Domain Name News

**What information do I collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on my site, subscribe to my weekly newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. If you fill out a form on my site, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit and read my site anonymously. If you’ve given me your name and email address, I may add you to my list of contacts. I may also include you in my list of contacts if you’ve connected with me on social networking sites like LinkedIn and provided your email address.

I regularly send out an email newsletter to all of my contacts. In any case, you can always opt out of receiving emails from me.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads if they’re on my site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

**What do I use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

; To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

; To improve my website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

; To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

; To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

; To send periodic emails

; To send periodic emails via an email newsletter

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. You can always opt out of receiving these emails from me.

**Do I use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

I use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone.

**Do I disclose any information to outside parties?**

I do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist me in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at my discretion, I may include or offer third party products or services on my website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. I therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, I seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because I value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. I therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

I am in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), I do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. My website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through my website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit my Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.billhartzer.com

**Your Consent**

By using my site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

**Changes to my Privacy Policy**

If I decide to change our privacy policy, I will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on September 8, 2014.

**Contacting Me**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact me using the information below.

https://www.billhartzer.com/

Bill Hartzer  
14601 Hyde Away lane  
Mabank, TX 75147  
USA  
bill@billhartzer.com  
214-236-4378
